What's with him?
His earlier momentum is gone.
So is his drive.
I feel confusion from his fist.
You're not being serious, are you?
That's not—
You don't wanna land that punch.
You don't wanna dodge my kick, either.
This fight...
I thought they picked it
because they knew everything.
But they didn't.
Then, why did he just punch them?
I want to know...
more about him.
What the hell are you tryin' to do?
Really...
What am I trying to do?
Why did you punch those guys?
You can do whatever in your team
as long as you have power, right?
That's right.
This is a place for the strong.
It's not a place for scumbags.
When you lose your mind,
the limbs no longer function properly.
Gradually, I ultimately spent more time
with skinning all the scumbags.
And that's when...
we got into a tussle
against Bofurin, Choji's obsession.
I thought it would trigger
some kind of change.
But we roped everyone into a fight
with no shred of justice for us.
Even then, there's no turning back.
Because on that day,
I decided to commit to this wrong path.
I cannot stop here.
This emblem has faded quite a bit.
What the hell are you tryin' to do?
Let's see...
I wanna head to the mountains.
Huh?
You lost in yourself?
You said this wasn't a place for scumbags.
Then what are you doing here?
Don't give me that nonsense.
You're doing what scumbags do,
just like them.
I'll admit it. You're strong.
But you're goddamn lame.
And to make you realize that,
I'm gonna win against you.
When that happens,
you're gonna stop bein' lame,
and become an awesome guy
that I wanna fight against!
That's quite selfish of you.
You've got some nerve to say that
to someone who clearly outclasses you.
Selfish? Hell yeah!
This is what it means to push your will through
in a fight, isn't it?
For me, no matter
how strong my opponent...
even if that guy saved my life...
I don't avert my eyes...
nor distort who I am!
Why does it end up that way?
Doing that won't make them stronger—
I'm the leader, right?
I'm the strongest. I'm free.
I won't yield to anyone.
I'm going to decide.
If you don't understand me,
then get out.
ORI
Fine.
But...
I'll tell everyone
about your views, Choji.
I'll do all the "skinning" too.
So Choji....
please keep smiling with the guys.
You really are good
at pushing people's buttons.
I knew it.
You weren't serious at all earlier.
Right, Scraggles?
I'm not Scraggles.
Name's Togame.
Jo Togame.
I get it.
Let's get to it...
Sakura.
Wh-What's up with them?
Th-Those guys...
They're laughing.
Sakura-kun,
you really are an amazing guy.
I don't really get it...
but it's really touched my heart.
Who would've thought...
Sakura could go this far?
Agreed.
Damn it.
What the hell?
I'm supposedly fighting a guy
who does really lame stuff.
So why does it feel so damn comfortable?
Besides...
If he says that to me as an opponent...
Let's get to it...
Sakura.
I've never been called by my name.
Sheesh.
He's having an irritating amount of fun here.
His movement is getting
better and better, too.
Now, bring it!
Man, I didn't know fights felt this good.
Ditto. I didn't know.
You've kept me company long enough.
Let's end it.
Yeah.
It was really fun.
Togame.
Sakura.
That's right.
For me, no matter
how strong my opponent...
even if that guy saved my life...
I don't avert my eyes...
nor distort who I am!
On that day...
This is what I should have done.
But I averted my eyes.
I didn't face him.
I didn't push through with who I was.
I'm sure you'll become
even stronger than you are now.
You're not afraid of pushing your will through,
no matter who you face.
Please don't ever change.
Thank you...
Sakura.
I finally understand now.
I can't stand up anymore.
I give up.
Huh? What'd he just...
Give up?
No way he said that!
He charges in laughing
even into dangerous situations!
This has gotta be a mistake!
Yeah.
S-Sakura-san.
Give me a break!
What was that at the end?
Why're you giving up?
Why'd you decide to lose on purpose!?
Okay, good work, good work.
You're so strong!
You should go against me sometime!
Now, Ume-chan, come on!
- Hey, I'm still not—
- It's finally our turn!
Choji.
- Hurry up! Hurry!
- We should call it off.
- C'mon, Ume-chan! Hey, Ume-chan!
- There's no justice for us here.
- Hey, come on! This is gonna be fun, right?
- We were...
- I was in the wrong.
- Hurry on over!
- Come on, let's get on with it!
- Choji...
Let's hurry up and fight!
Shut up already.
You lost, so you stay quiet.
Sakura.
It's time to swap.
I'm glad.
Looks like you had a proper conversation.
Your action right now
is the best proof of that.
You too, Togame.
Can you leave the rest up to me?
Please.
You're quite the busybody.
Don't die, okay?
If you lose...
I'll beat you up.
Sure.
Why does it piss me off so much?
I should be used to someone else
getting beat up.
So why...
I'm glad.
Looks like you had a proper conversation.
I don't get it at all.
I didn't hear any words from my fists.
Sakura-san.
Welcome back.
Nire-kun is crying again.
That was so amazing. It touched my heart!
Sakura.
I'm sure you don't like it, but that last bit
was Togame's way of setting things right.
Even without that,
you did really well.
Now, Ume-chan...
We can finally fight!
Gotta ask you one thing.
Did you feel anything
from watching that fight just now?
Huh? Feel what?
I see.
What a shame.
A shame?
Why?
Oh, well.
Anyway, Ume-chan,
it really is unfair! So unfair!
Bofurin has so many strong kids.
It's nothing like us.
Because everyone is so weak,
I can't become free.
It's no fun.
What the hell?
Is that what Tomiyama-san really thinks of us?
But if I win, Ume-chan and Furin
will become all mine!
Ume-chan, you're the top of Furin,
so you're stronger and freer
than anyone else in Furin.
That's why you look like
you're having so much fun, right?
If I can prove that I'm stronger than you,
Ume-chan, and get Furin for myself,
this time for sure I'll be free
and have more fun than anyone else.
Finally...
Finally....
Finally, these boring days will end.
Now, Ume-chan...
Hand it over...
to me!
I've never seen such reckless movements.
He's a natural born monster.
Of course. He became the youngest leader
in Shishitoren history.
Damn it. Damn it.
If he didn't stop me back there....
And against him, too...
Damn it!
I'll make sure to get stronger.
More... A lot more!
Hey, Tomiyama.
What is it, Ume-chan?
It's gonna stay rough as long as you say
woulda-coulda-shoulda.
Tomiyama, you had it rough, huh?
As I said...
All this talk, Ume-chan.
You don't make any sense!
I see.
So you don't get it.
Against someone who can't understand
something so simple...
I'm 100% sure...
I won't lose.
SUCCEEDING THE PAST
Tomiyama-san's acrobatic movements
are amazing!
I-I can do stuff like that, too.
Really? That's amazing!
I wanna see it!
Huh? Right now?
Right now!
So you can't do it after all?
Oh? I'll show you how it's done!
- Oh, yippee!
- Here goes!
Three, two, one...
H-Hold on a sec!
I'll do it on my own timing!
Ready...